Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- General Photographs, 1960-2002; Series III; 10.3 linear feet (26 boxes)
  - Color Slides and Transparencies
    - Copy Photographs
      Copy photographs that chiefly document published photographs by Palmquist, as well as his artwork.
      - Advertisements (Box 36)
      - Artwork (Box 36)
      - Century 21 Exposition (Box 36)
      - Christmas flood of 1964 (Box 36)
      - Feature stories and items (Box 36)
      - Humboldt State College (Box 36)
      - Logging and Arcata Jubilee (Box 36)
      - Photograph prize winners (Box 36)
      - Portfolio (Box 36)
      - Portraits (Box 36)
      - Pottery (Box 36)
      - Shasta State Historical Monument and Fort Ross (Box 36)
        Includes images of the monument where Carl Palmquist worked as a state park attendant.
      - Theater and performing arts (Box 36)
      - Travel photography (Box 36)
      - "A Visit with Grandma" (Box 36)
        A photographically illustrated essay by Ruth Crane about her grandmother Stella H. Crane, with photographs by Palmquist.
- Wedding Photographs, 1960-circa 1990; Series IV; 11.9 linear feet (11 boxes)
  Series III is organized with negatives arranged alphabetically by the name or initial of the bride followed by unidentified negatives and photographic prints.
  This portion of the collection consists of circa 5,000 to 7,500 black-and-white and color negatives with dimensions of 35 millimeters and 120 millimeters, as well as some 4 by 5 inches, of weddings chiefly in Humboldt County created by Palmquist and housed in his original envelopes, circa 1960-circa 1990, as well as around 100 photographic prints. Some envelopes includes notes about the bride, groom, and locations, although most have no dates and many refer to the couples by the initials of their surnames.
  - A.C. to B.W., circa 1960-circa 1990; 36 (Box 37)
  - C. to Dyar-Harrison, circa 1960-circa 1990; 44 (Box 38)
  - E.-M. to Hamilton-Wallingford, circa 1960-circa 1990; 40 (Box 39)
  - Hanna-Borges to K.-C., circa 1960-circa 1990; 41 (Box 40)
  - Kea to L.-R., circa 1960-circa 1990; 39 (Box 41)
  - L.-S. to Palmrose-Carlson, circa 1960-circa 1990; 44 (Box 42)
  - Pasquini-Robertson to Ross, circa 1960-circa 1990; 37 (Box 43)
  - Rylander to Tunzini-Mullens, circa 1960-circa 1990; 42 (Box 44)
  - Venn-Moe to W.L., circa 1960-circa 1990; 16 (Box 45)
  - Unidentified, circa 1960-circa 1990; 84 (Box 46)
  - Unidentified photographic prints, circa 1960-circa 1990 (Box 47)
- Humboldt State University, 1962-1972; Series V; 5.7 linear feet (16 boxes)
  Series IV is organized into five subseries: Theater Arts Department; General Negatives and Photographic Prints; General Photographic Prints; General Color Slides and Transparencies; and Oversize
  Photographs of Humboldt State University, Arcata, California, which Palmquist created or collected as a staff photographer from 1961 until his retirement in 1989. This portion of the collection also includes non-campus images used to illustrate university publications. A large portion of this component includes photographic documentation of the Theater Arts Department.
  Biographical/Historical note
  Humboldt State Normal School was founded in 1913. In 1921 the name changed to Humboldt State Teachers College and then in 1935 to Humboldt State College. In 1972, it changed its name to California State University, Humboldt, and then to Humboldt State University in 1974.
  - Theater Arts Department
    Organized under four headings: Negatives and Contact Prints, Negatives and Color Transparencies, Photographic Prints, and Publications
    Photographs of productions and activities of the Theater Arts Department at Humboldt State College, March 1962-May 1972.
    - Negatives and Contact Prints
      Arranged chronologically.
      Negatives and strips of contact prints from black-and-white negatives with dimensions of 35 millimeters that document theatrical productions. The material is housed in negative pages numbered and annotated by Palmquist.
      - Bells are Ringing (1-15), 1962 March; 15 (Box 48)
      - Six Characters in Search of an Author (16-17), 1962 May; 2 (Box 48)
      - One/Two Time (18-19), 1962 May; 2 (Box 48)
      - Aunty Mame (20-27), 1962 June; 8 (Box 48)
      - The Uniontown Players (28-45), 1962 July; 18 (Box 48)
      - Sheba (46-50), 1962 July; 5 (Box 48)
      - Varieties (51-53), 1962 July; 3 (Box 48)
      - Fumed Oak (54-55), 1962 July; 2 (Box 48)
      - Marriage Proposal (56-57), 1962 July; 2 (Box 48)
      - The Chairs (58-62), 1962 October; 5 (Box 48)
      - My Heart's in the Highlands (63-68), 1962 October; 6 (Box 48)
      - The Innocents (69-79), 1962 October; 11 (Box 48)
      - Guys and Dolls (80-87), 1962 November; 8 (Box 48)
      - Look Homeward Angel (88-95), 1962 December; 8 (Box 48)
      - The Medium (96-98), 1962 December; 3 (Box 48)
      - Captain Lovelock (99-100), 1962 December; 2 (Box 48)
      - Oedipus Rex (101-109), 1963 February; 9 (Box 49)
      - Life with Father (110-113), 1963 May; 4 (Box 49)
      - Charley's Aunt (114-128), 1963 May; 15 (Box 49)
      - Deadly Game (129-143), 1963 October; 15 (Box 49)
      - La Ronde (144-159), 1963 December; 16 (Box 49)
      - La Ronde, backstage (160-174), 1963 December; 15 (Box 49)
      - The Crucible (175-188), 1964 April; 14 (Box 49)
      - Theater brochure designed by Peter Palmquist (189-190), 1964; 2 (Box 49)
      - Pirates of Penzance (191-202), 1964 May; 12 (Box 49)
      - Theater faculty, including John Van Duzer (1904-1974) (203-204), 1964; 2 (Box 50)
      - Midsummer Night's Dream (205-221), 1964 October; 17 (Box 50)
      - One-Way Pendulum (222-235), 1964 December; 14 (Box 50)
      - Man Who Sings (236-238), 1965 February; 3 (Box 50)
      - Desire Under the Elms (239-244), 1965 March; 6 (Box 50)
      - Hello Out There! (245-249), 1965 April; 5 (Box 50)
      - Dark of the Moon (250-266), 1965 May; 17 (Box 50)
      - Mother (267-268), 1965 May; 2 (Box 50)
      - Caesar and Cleopatra (269-279), 1965 October; 11 (Box 50)
      - Right You Are (280-284), 1965 December; 5 (Box 50)
      - The Tavern (285-289), 1966 February; 5 (Box 50)
      - Sondelis (290-298), 1966 April; 9 (Box 50)
      - The Brig (299), 1966 December (Box 50)
      - Troilus and Cressida (300-307), 1966 October; 8 (Box 51)
      - The Graduation (308), 1966 December (Box 51)
      - Strolling Players (309-310), 1966 May; 2 (Box 51)
      - Saints' Day (311-321), 1967 January; 11 (Box 51)
      - The Visit (322-327), 1967 February; 6 (Box 51)
      - The Wind in the Willows (328-332), 1967 May; 5 (Box 51)
      - Summer Theater Institute (333-340), 1967 Summer; 8 (Box 51)
        Hosts: Phil Mann, Richard Rothrock
        Guest: Mercer
      - Belcher's Luck (341-367), 1967; 27 (Box 51)
      - Eh? (363-372), 1967; 10 (Box 51)
      - Automobile Graveyard (373-386), 1967; 14 (Box 51)
      - Five Pots Full (387-388), 1967 April; 2 (Box 51)
      - The Fantastics (389-401), 1967 December; 13 (Box 51)
      - The American Dream (402), 1967 March (Box 52)
      - The Alchemist (403-418), 1967 October; 16 (Box 52)
      - Morality Plays (419-426), 1967 December; 8 (Box 52)
      - Opera, Opera (427-428), 1968 February; 2 (Box 52)
      - Little Squire Gullible (429-437), 1968 February; 9 (Box 52)
      - Libre (438-441), 1968 March; 4 (Box 52)
      - Bernada Alba (442-445), 1968 March; 4 (Box 52)
      - College Elementary School play (446-448), 1968 April; 3 (Box 52)
      - Cinematography and mime classes (449-450), 1968 April; 2 (Box 52)
      - The Streets of New York (451-461), 1968 May; 11 (Box 52)
      - Children's Theater Institute (462-466), 1968 July; 5 (Box 52)
      - Way of the World (467-474), 1968 July; 8 (Box 52)
      - Litany of Molock (475-488), 1968 July; 14 (Box 52)
      - Dylan (489-500), 1968 October; 12 (Box 52)
      - Governor's Lady (501), 1968 November (Box 53)
      - Movement class (502-503), 1968 December; 2 (Box 53)
      - Look Back in Anger (504-508), 1969 February; 5 (Box 53)
      - Mandrake Root (509-510), 1969 February; 2 (Box 53)
      - Breeze in the Moonlight (511-521), 1969 March; 11 (Box 53)
      - Merry Wives of Windsor (opera) (522), 1696 February (Box 53)
      - One act plays (523-524), 1969 April; 2 (Box 53)
      - The Emperor's New Clothes (525-532), 1969 April; 8 (Box 53)
      - Master of Arts project of Richard E. Dart (1926-1988) (533-536), 1969 April; 4 (Box 53)
      - Yass Hawakawa (537), 1969 April (Box 53)
      - Macbeth (538-541), 1969 May; 4 (Box 53)
      - Master of Arts show of Judith Shogren (542-546), 1969 May; 7 (Box 53)
      - Mime (547-550), 1969 Summer; 4 (Box 53)
      - Serpent of Ai (551-557), 1969 July; 7 (Box 53)
      - Children's Show (558-560), 1969 Summer; 3 (Box 53)
      - Dance of the Early Morning (561-564), 1969 Summer; 5 (Box 53)
      - Everyplace People (565-572), 1969 August; 8 (Box 53)
      - Waiting for Godot (573-576), 1969 October; 4 (Box 53)
      - Publicity for faculty members Jean A. Bazemore, Gerald F. Beck, and Gillespie (577-578), 1969 November; 2 (Box 53)
      - September Tea (579-584), 1969 December; 6 (Box 53)
      - Night Must Fall (585-592), 1970 February; 8 (Box 53)
      - Skin of Our Teeth, backstage (593-603), 1970 February; 11 (Box 53)
      - Skin of Our Teeth (604-608), 1970 March; 5 (Box 54)
      - Mime (609-612), 1970 April; 4 (Box 54)
      - Alice in Wonderland (613-615), 1970 April; 3 (Box 54)
      - Opera workshop (616), 1970 April (Box 54)
      - The Bedbug (617-619), 1970 May; 3 (Box 54)
      - Three Asians (620-621), 1970 July; 2 (Box 54)
      - Dr. Faustus (622), 1970 October (Box 54)
      - Dracula (623-625), 1970 July; 3 (Box 54)
      - Mime (626-631), 1970 November; 6 (Box 54)
      - Honsa (632-641), 1970 November; 10 (Box 54)
      - One act plays (642-644), 1971 February; 3 (Box 54)
      - The Drunkard (645-652), 1971 February; 8 (Box 54)
      - Vasco (653-660), 1971 June; 8 (Box 54)
      - Summer opera (661), 1971 August (Box 54)
      - The Birthday Party (662-663), 1971 November; 2 (Box 54)
      - One acts (664), 1971 March (Box 54)
      - Caucasian Chalk Circle (665-668), 1972 March; 4 (Box 54)
      - Opera (669-671), 1972 April; 3 (Box 54)
      - Magical Bugs (672-677), 1972 April; 6 (Box 54)
      - Penny for a Song (678-683), 1972 May; 6 (Box 54)
      - Unidentified Production (684a-689) (Box 54)
    - Negatives and Color Transparencies
      Color Transparencies and negatives that document unidentified productions.
      - Negatives (Box 55)
      - Transparencies, 4 (Box 55)
    - Photographic Prints
      - Skin of Our Teeth, 1970 March (Box 56)
      - Alice in Wonderland, 1970 April (Box 56)
      - The Bedbug, 1970 May (Box 56)
      - The Drunkard, 1971 February (Box 56)
      - Vasco, 1971 June (Box 56)
      - The Birthday Party, 1971 November (Box 56)
      - Magical Bugs, 1972 April (Box 56)
      - Unidentified productions (Box 56)
      - Oversize photographic prints for unidentified productions, 24 (Box 57)
    - Publications
      Arranged alphabetically.
      Publications distributed or related to the Theater Arts Department created by Palmquist or reproducing his photographs.
      - Broadsides, 2 (Box 58)
      - Brochure and mock-up, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Brochure Folio, 2 folders (Box 59)
        Brochure folio with high-contrast photographs created by Palmquist that represent productions by the Theater Arts Department
        - Mock-ups, 1972; 5 (Box 59)
        - Source photographs and negatives
          - Cover and Print Numbers 1-7, 1972; 8 (Box 59)
          - Print Numbers 8-20, 1972; 13 (Box 60)
        - Alternate photographs, 21 folders (Box 61)
      - Leaflets, 8 (Box 58)
      - Newspaper tear sheets (Box 62 (Broadside))
      - Pamphlet (Box 58)
      - Posters related to productions by the Theater Arts Department at Humboldt State College, undated (Box 63 (Broadside))
  - General Negatives and Photographic Prints
    - Brochure negatives, 1968 December (Box 64)
    - Building program, 1958-1959 (Box 64)
    - Campus buildings (Box 64)
    - Campus buildings, snow-covered, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Campus general, including dancing, dormitories, and visiting film maker, Ousmane Sembène (Box 64)
    - Campus radio station (Box 64)
    - Commencement, 1958-1971; 7 (Box 64)
    - Faculty
      - Berry, Glenn, and Dennis Anderson (Box 64)
      - Carranco, Lynwood (Box 64)
      - Spaid, Stanley, 1969 June (Box 64)
    - Field hockey (Box 64)
    - Folk dancers at Sequoia Plaza, 1972 May 1 (Box 64)
    - Groups (Box 64)
    - Homecoming, 1964-1968; 5 (Box 64)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von, copy photograph of a painting (Box 64)
    - Kite marathon, 1968 March 30 (Box 64)
    - Logs for Indian canoes at Korbel, California, 1970 Spring (Box 64)
    - Lumberjack Days (Box 64)
    - Maharishi Mahesh Yogi visit, 1970 August (Box 64)
    - Marine Laboratory at Trinidad, California, site for mammal tank, 1968 April (Box 64)
    - Music programs, 1961-1970 (Box 64)
    - Nursing students, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Performing arts (Box 64)
    - Registration, 1963-1964 (Box 64)
    - Sea Grant project led by George Allen, 1971 February-June (Box 64)
    - Student organizations, 1961-1970 (Box 64)
    - Students
      - Hasper, Rich, at the campus radio station, 1969 May (Box 64)
      - Huffman and Burnham (Box 64)
      - Richardson, Jim, student teacher with children, 1964 December (Box 64)
    - Students and classes (Box 64)
    - Visual arts (Box 64)
  - General Photographic Prints
    - Basketball (Box 64)
    - Campus buildings, interiors (Box 64)
    - Century 21 Exposition in Seattle, Washington, classroom instruction, and redwood forests (Job Number 3052), 1962 (Box 64)
    - Faculty
      - Display about distinguished faculty at Humboldt State College, circa 1970 (Box 64)
      - Day, Richard C. (Box 64)
      - Householder, James E. (Box 64)
    - Fish hatchery (Box 64)
    - Siemens, Cornelius Henry, president of Humboldt State College, 1950 to 1973, 1962
      - Siemens at the dedication of the Forestry Building (Box 64)
      - Siemens with Governor Edmund Gerald Brown, Sr., and Homer Balabanis (Box 64)
    - Students and classes (Box 64)
    - Track and field (Box 64)
  - General Color Slides and Transparencies
    - Campus directory, copy photograph, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Fountain, Gene and Susie Baker (Box 64)
  - Oversize
    - Audiovisual equipment (Box 65)
    - Campus radio station (Box 65)
    - Performing arts (Box 65)
    - Students and classes (Box 65)
- Christmas Flood of 1964, Series VI; 0.79 linear feet (4 boxes)
  Photographs of the Christmas flood of 1964, a major flood that took place in the Pacific Northwest and California between December 18, 1964 and January 7, 1965. Palmquist created many of the newspaper photographs attributed to the Associated Press and United Press Syndicate.
  - News photographs, 1964 December; 9 (Box 66)
    News photographs created by Palmquist and others for the Associated Press.
  - Photographs attributed to Palmquist, 1964 December-January; 3 (Box 66)
  - Oversize photographs attributed to Palmquist, 1964 December-January
    - Buildings, 1964 December-January; 21 (Box 67)
    - Landscapes, 22 (Box 68)
    - Rescues and rebuilding, 1964 December-January; 13 (Box 69)
- Logging Road in the Jackson Demonstration State Forest, 1967; Series VII; 0.21; (1 box)
  Photographs created by Palmquist as part of a study by the California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection that document the construction of main and spur haul logging roads constructed in the South Fork Watershed of Caspar Creek in the Jackson Demonstration State Forest in Mendocino County, California, June-August 1967.
  - Notes, 1967 June-August (Box 70)
  - Prints, 1967 June-August (Box 70)
  - Negatives, 1967 June-August (Box 70)
  - Original Housing, 1967 June-August; 2 (Box 70)
- Nudes, circa 1973; Series VIII; 0.42; (1 box)
  Black-and-white negatives, contact prints, and photographic prints of female nudes created by Palmquist and possibly others. Many of these images apeared in an exhibition, Toad Hill, Other Nonsense and Jennifer, at Humboldt State University, probably in February 1974.
  - Negatives, 35 millimeters, circa 1973; 170 negatives (Box 71)
  - Negatives, 120 millimeters, circa 1973; 48 negatives (Box 71)
  - Negatives, 4 by 5 inches, and contact prints, circa 1973; 68 negatives (Box 71)
  - Contact prints, circa 1973; 4 folders (Box 71)
  - Photographic prints, circa 1973; 3 (Box 71)
  - Nudes (Box 71)
  - Transparencies, circa 1973; 3 (Box 71)
  - Notes, circa 1973 (Box 71)
- Copy Photographs, undated; Series IX; 8.1 linear feet (32 boxes)
  Series VIII is organized into three subseries: Negatives and Photographic Prints, Photographic Prints, Color Slides
  Copy photographs made by Palmquist and others of work by chiefly by unidentified photographers and repositories, except where noted. The copy photographs chiefly relate to research projects and presentations by Palmquist.
  - Negatives and Photographic Prints
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Mixed subjects: studio portraits of men and newspaper clippings (Box 72)
    - Siskiyou County, California, 147 negatives (Box 73)
      Black-and-white negatives, 4 by 5 inches, probably copied from a repository in Siskiyou County.
    - Stereographs, photographs of glass examples (Box 72)
    - Studio portraits
      - Children (Box 72)
      - Men (Box 72)
      - Men and women (Box 72)
  - Photographic Prints
    - American Indians
      - Exterior portraits and scenes (Box 72)
      - Interiors (Box 72)
      - Paintings (Box 72)
      - Studio portraits (Box 72)
    - Carleton Watkins photographs (Box 72)
    - Cased Photographs (Box 72)
    - Chinese immigrants in the United States (Box 72)
    - Downieville, California (Box 72)
    - Drawings and prints (Box 72)
    - Exteriors (Box 72)
    - Informal portraits
      - Animals and people (Box 72)
      - Children (Box 72)
      - Men and women (Box 72)
      - Musicians (Box 72)
      - Women (Box 72)
    - Interiors (Box 72)
    - Mixed subjects: newspaper clippings and studio portraits (Box 72)
    - Stereograph card verso for photographs by A. R. Treat (Box 72)
    - Studio portraits and informal portraits
      - Animals (Box 74)
      - Animals with people (Box 74)
      - Children (Box 74)
      - Men (Box 74)
      - Men and Women (Box 74)
      - Musicians (Box 74)
      - Women (Box 74)
    - Trinity County Museum, Weaverville, California (Box 74)
  - Color Slides
    Organized under eight headings: Male Photographers; Women Photographers; Stereograph Photographers and Publishers; Photographic Processes, Formats, and Equipment; California Sites and Subjects; Historical Subjects; General Research and Presentations; and Slides from Workspace
    Color slides created and collected by Palmquist to illustrate presentations on the history of photography and support his research projects.
    The slides are housed in slide holder sheets in three-ring binders with dividers that designate groups established by Palmquist.
    - Male Photographers
      - Anderson, G. E. (Box 75)
      - Anderson, Hugh (Box 75)
      - Atget (Box 75)
      - Baker, R. J. (Box 75)
      - Bell, W. A. (Box 75)
      - Blum, Robert (Box 75)
      - Boysen, J. T. (Box 75)
      - Brady (Box 75)
      - Britt, Peter (Box 75)
      - Bruff, J. G. (Box 75)
      - Carr, Richard (Box 75)
      - Chase, A.W. (Box 75)
      - Cherry, Edgar (Box 75)
      - Clayton, James A. (Box 75)
      - Coombs, Fred (Box 76)
      - Coon, Floyd (Box 76)
      - Daguerre (Box 76)
      - Fardon, G. R. (Box 76)
      - Fiske, George (Box 76)
      - Ford, James M. (Box 76)
      - Frassanito, William A. (Box 76)
      - Frith, Francis (Box 76)
      - Genthe, Arnold (Box 76)
      - Grant, M. H. (Box 76)
      - Hart, A. A. (Box 76)
      - Haynes, F. J. (Box 76)
      - Heller, Louis (Box 76)
      - Hillers, John K. (Box 77)
      - Hime, H. L. (Box 77)
      - Hine, Lewis (Box 77)
      - Holmes, Alex (Box 77)
      - Houseworth, Thomas (Box 77)
      - Jackson, W. H. (Box 77)
      - Kinsley (Box 77)
      - Kusel, E. A. (Box 77)
      - Lange, William (Box 77)
      - Muybridge, Eadweard J. (Box 77)
      - Nesemann, E. (Box 77)
      - O'Sullivan, Timothy (Box 77)
      - Pond, C. L. (Box 77)
      - Reilly, J. J. (Box 77)
      - Riis, Jacob and Hine (Box 78)
      - Russell, A. J. (Box 78)
      - Seely Brothers (Box 78)
      - Shlear, Robert (Box 78)
      - Southworth, Nancy, and Josiah J. Hawes (Box 78)
      - Steichen, Edward (Box 78)
      - Stieglitz, et. al. (Box 78)
      - Strand, Paul (Box 78)
      - Talbot, William Fox (Box 78)
      - Towne, Paul (Box 78)
      - Van Sant, J. (Box 78)
      - Weed, Charles L. (Box 78)
      - White, Clarence (Box 78)
      - Male photographers, subjects
        - Directory of 19th Century California Photographers, 2 (Box 79)
        - Advertisements for Humboldt County Photographers (Box 79)
        - Photographers and studios (Box 79)
        - Photographers, general (Box 79)
    - Women Photographers
      - Abbott, Berenice (Box 80)
      - Armer, Laura Adams (Box 80)
      - Atkins, Anna (Box 80)
      - Auger, Lina (Box 80)
      - Austin, Alice (Box 80)
      - Ayers, Lizzie (Box 80)
      - Baldin, Maud (Box 80)
      - Beals, Jessie Tarbox (Box 80)
      - Boughtman, Alice (Box 80)
      - Bourke-White, Margaret (Box 80)
      - Bowman, Ethel C. (Box 81)
      - Brigman, Anne (Box 81)
      - Broom, Mrs. Albert (Box 81)
      - Cameron, Evelyn (Box 81)
      - Cameron, Julia Margaret (Box 81)
      - Cardozo, Abbie (Box 81)
      - Carpenter, Helen (Box 81)
      - Consindas, Marie (Box 81)
      - Cruikshank, Abigail (Box 81)
      - Cunningham, Imogen (Box 81)
      - Emmons, Chansonetta S. (Box 81)
      - Freeman, Emma B. (Box 81)
      - Freeman Art Co. (Box 82)
      - Garrett, Edna (Box 82)
      - Gay, E. Jane (Box 82)
      - Gilpin, Laura (Box 82)
      - Halsey, Louise (Box 82)
      - Hanscom, Adelaide (Box 82)
      - Hawarden, Clementina (Box 82)
      - Hudson, Miss (Box 82)
      - Johnston, Frances B. (Box 82)
      - Kanaga, Consuelo (Box 82)
      - Kasebier, Gertrude (Box 82)
      - Kemmler, Florence B. (Box 82)
      - Klute, Jeannette (Box 82)
      - Lange, Dorothea (Box 82)
      - Lavensons, Alma (Box 82)
      - Jacobi, Lotte (Box 82)
      - MacAdams, Cynthia (Box 82)
      - Mather, Margrethe (Box 82)
      - Matthews, Kate (Box 82)
      - Matson, Fannie (Box 83)
      - Maynard, Hannah (Box 83)
      - McGraw, Nellie (Box 83)
      - Metzner, Sheila (Box 83)
      - Mondotti, Tina (Box 83)
      - Morris, Ella M. (Box 83)
      - Noskowiah, Sonya (Box 83)
      - O'Conner, Mrs. D. L. (Box 83)
      - Parker, Olivia (Box 83)
      - Pitchford, Emily (Box 83)
      - Ramsour, Malvina (Box 83)
      - Resnick, Marcia (Box 83)
      - Rudolph, Mrs. J. F. (Box 83)
      - Shannon, Mrs. Julia (Box 83)
      - Tate, Mrs. M. J. (Box 83)
      - Tyler, Mrs. M. E. (Box 83)
      - Winslow, Mary (Box 83)
      - Withington, Mrs. E. W. (Box 83)
      - Wolcott, Marion Post (Box 83)
      - Women photographers, subjects
        - Women in Photography (Box 84)
        - Black women (Box 84)
        - Women with cameras (Box 84)
        - Women photographers, logos (Box 84)
        - Women, images of, 2 (Box 84)
        - Women photographers, advertisements (Box 84)
        - Women photographers (Box 84)
        - Women retouchers (Box 84)
        - Women photographers in the 1970s (Box 84)
        - Blatant Image, magazine of feminist photography (Box 84)
    - Stereograph Photographers and Publishers
      - Abell to Mills (Box 85)
      - Moulton to Yosemite Valley (Box 86)
      - General stereographs
        - 1860s (Box 87)